Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Studio Portraits (Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 12 July 1970; ref482; Studio Al Assime, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref483; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.6 x 3.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., 19 October 1949; ref484; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Men; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a turtleneck., 1 August 1972; ref485; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref486; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 3.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref487; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 6.7 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref488; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref489; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 9 December 1957; ref490; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref491; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.1 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Men; Facial Hair; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref492; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - A studio portrait of a man with tinted glasses wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref493; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 6.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a beard., Circa 1955-1975; ref494; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref495; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing graduation robes., Circa 1955-1975; ref496; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Men; Academic Dress; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., Circa 1955-1975; ref497; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.1 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Facial Hair; Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., 1 August 1964; ref498; Studio Rateb, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Facial Hair; Men; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 30 November 1971; ref499; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Arabic Writing; Syria; Men; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref500; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.6 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., 1962; ref501; Photo Paroun, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a striped shirt., 17 May 1964; ref502; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 3.6 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref503; 1 Photographic Prints; 2.7 x 2.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Arabic Writing; Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref504; 1 Photographic Prints; 3.8 x 3.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Men; Syria; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., 24 November 1961; ref505; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Facial Hair; Men; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref506; Studio Najah, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref507; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., 24 October 1958; ref508; Studio Carmen, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., 3 June 1972; ref509; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Facial Hair; Men; Arabic Writing; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., 23 May 1961; ref510; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.1 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., 4 September 1955; ref511; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Men; Facial Hair; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref512; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.7 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., February 1941; ref513; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref514; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., October 1971; ref515; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 x 3.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., Circa 1955-1975; ref516; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., 24 December 1969; ref517; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a plaid shirt., 30 July 1959; ref518; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 26 February 1972; ref519; Ali Baba, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.2 x 4.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a light mustache., 11 February 1972; ref520; Studio Housam (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref521; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - A studio portrait of a man., November 1971; ref522; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., 1959; ref523; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 3.7 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 19 July 1966; ref524; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Men; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref525; 1 Photographic Prints; 4 x 3.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., 8 March 1955; ref526; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1962; ref527; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 21 July 1961; ref528; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref529; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 3.7 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref530; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.1 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., 3 November 1969; ref531; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.6 x 3.5 m (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Boys; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children
  - A portrait of a boy in front of a field., Circa 1955-1975; ref532; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.9 x 3.6 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Boys; Children; Outdoors; Clocks/Watches; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 13 November 1972; ref533; Studio Al-Kindi, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref534; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Arabic Writing; Syria; Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref535; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.1 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref536; Studio Najah, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a striped shirt., 5 November 1982; ref537; Studio Zaven, Aleppo (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 4 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Jewelry; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref538; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing striped clothing., Circa 1955-1975; ref539; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 3.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Women; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a woman., 10 August 1972; ref540; Studio Le Caire, Rue Fardos, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Arabic Writing; Damascus, Syria; Women; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref541; Studio Sameer, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Men; Uniforms; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., 14 March 1961; ref542; Studio Rateb, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Syria; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a little girl., 16 April 1972; ref543; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Children; Girls; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., 3 April 1982; ref544; Studio Suri Ramis (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - A studio portrait of a young man with a beard., 8 June 1958; ref545; Manuel A&P (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing a pearl necklace., Circa 1955-1975; ref546; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Women; Jewelry; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref547; Studio Khallaf, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man., 3 July 1972; ref548; Yacoub Touranian, Jordan; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.1 x 6.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - A heart-shaped studio portrait of a boy., 27 August 1959; ref549; Studio Al Assime, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Boys; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria; Children
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref550; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.1 x 6.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref551; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Men; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a young woman wearing a striped shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref552; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Women; Jewelry; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman wearing patterned skirt outside., 1954; ref553; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Women; Outdoors; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man in a striped shirt., 2 April 1970; ref554; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.5 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing glasses and a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref555; Studio Carmen, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref556; Studio Najah, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 19 November 1969; ref557; Photo Al Andalous, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1972; ref558; Above Cinema Mounir, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Boys; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children
  - A studio portrait of a boy., March 1970; ref559; Studio Al Khayyam, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref560; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1971; ref561; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.8 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 15 July 1987; ref562; Qusai, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.8 x 6.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Aleppo, Syria; Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 1984; ref563; Qusai, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.6 x 6.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref564; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A studio portrait of one man in two outfits, a suit and a military uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref565; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Facial Hair; Syria; Men
  - A studio portrait of one man in two outfits, a turtleneck and a military uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref566; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of two men in uniform smiling., Circa 1955-1975; ref567; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Syria; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Medals/Insignia
  - A group portrait with a man in uniform, a woman wearing glasses, and four little girls wearing bows., 17 August 1981; ref568; Photo Monsour, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Children; Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Jewelry; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., 12 February 1973; ref569; Studio Minas (Chouhada, Salhiyeh, Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 1980; ref570; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref571; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Boys; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Children
- Vernacular Series (Box 4)
  - A group portrait of six young men sitting outdoors., 24 October 1970; ref572; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a woman and two smiling children outside (linked ref 574)., Circa 1965-1975; ref573; Apamis, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Women; Children; Girls; Boys; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of a woman and a man in military uniform outside (linked ref 573)., Circa 1965-1975; ref574; Apamis, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Men; Women; Uniforms; Outdoors; Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Medals/Insignia
  - A group portrait of six young men in front of mountains., 4 March 1970; ref575; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Mountains/Hills; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors
  - A portrait of two young men on a patio., 24 October 1970; ref576; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Damascus, Syria; Mountains/Hills; Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of two men in suits, including Jareh Krikorian, and a small boy outside next to a car., Circa 1965-1975; ref577; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 6.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Children; Outdoors; Cars/Trucks; Streets/Roads; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Transportation
  - A group portrait of seven men wearing jackets in the snow., 4 March 1970; ref578; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Snow; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman with a gun, and two small boys., Circa 1965-1975; ref579; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Arabic Writing; Syria; Women; Men; Guns; Weapons; Children; Boys; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men looking at a fabric sample., Circa 1965-1975; ref580; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Advertisements; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Shops; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of nine men eating near a body of water., Circa 1965-1975; ref581; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Water; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Cigarettes; Radios; Hats; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Smoking; Food; Drinks/Beverages
  - Two women standing outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref583; Samir Color Lab, Saudi Arabia; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Women; Head Covers/Veils; Jewelry; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Saudi Arabia; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of six men sitting on a bench., Circa 1955-1975; ref584; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Outdoors; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Group Portraits